Finding Aid for the Fred Russell Initial Sort
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Newspapermen/ Reporters
  - Fitzgerald, Scotty (Box 17)
  - Fox, Bill Dinner, 1962 (Box 17)
  - Green, Ted (Box 17)
  - Green, Waxo Party Sep. 26th (Box 17)
  - Hearst, William Randolph (Box 17)
  - Hemingway, Ernest (Box 17)
  - Hooker, John J. (Box 17)
  - Jenkins, Burris (Box 17)
  - Keeler, O. B. (Box 17)
  - Lockert, Lacy (Box 17)
  - Lockert, Lacy Football Picks (Box 17)
  - McGill, Ralph (Box 17)
  - McLemore, Henry (Box 17)
  - Moss, Charles (Box 17)
  - Murphy, Jack (Box 17)
  - Nathan, George Jean (Box 17)
  - Norman, Jack (Box 17)
  - Pegler, Westbrook (Box 17)
  - Rice, Grantland (Box 17)
  - Rice, Grantland (Box 17)
  - Rice, Grantland (Box 17)
  - Rice, Grantland (Box 17)
  - Rice, Grantland (Box 17)
  - Rice, Grantland (Box 17)
  - Rice, Grantland- Charles Fountain Biography Proposal (Box 17)
  - Rice, Grantland- Dinner at Toots Shor’s, Oct 31, 1954 (Box 17)
  - Runyon, Damon (Box 17)
  - Salsinger, H.G. (Box 17)
  - Smith, Red (Box 17)
  - Smith, Red Lecture in Journalism (Box 17)
  - Smith, Red Collection at Notre Dame (Box 17)
  - Stahlman, James Geddes (Box 17)
  - Stahlman, James Geddes (Box 17)
  - Ward, Arch (Box 17)
  - Ward, Arch (Box 17)
  - Publishers-Editors-Newspapers (Box 17)
  - Outstanding Newsmen, Editors, Reporters (Box 17)
  - Newsmen (Box 17)
- Olympics
  - Olympics- 1960 History of Olympics (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1960 Rome Media Guides (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1960 Rome Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1960 Olympic Records (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1960 Olympic Trip (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1964 Tokyo Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1964 Tokyo Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1968 Mexico City Olympics, Track and Field (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1968 Mexico City Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1972 Munich Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1972 Munich Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1972 Munich Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1972 Munich Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1972 Munich Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1972 Munich Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1972 Munich Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1972 Munich Olympics Materials, TSU (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1976 Montreal Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1976 Montreal Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1976 Montreal Olympics Materials, Schedule, Hotel, Tickets (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1976 Montreal Olympics Materials, Track and Field (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1980 Lake Placid Winter Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1980 Moscow Olympics Materials, US Olympic Team Directory (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1980 Moscow Olympics Materials, Russian Publications (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1980 Moscow Olympics Materials, U.S.O.C. Position for the 1980 Games (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1984 Los Angeles Olympics Materials, Publications (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1988 Calgary Winter Olympics Materials, Publications (Box 18)
  - Olympics- 1988 Seoul Olympics Materials (Box 18)
  - Books- 1976 Olympic Guide by John V. Grombach (Box 18)
  - Books- 1980 Guinness Book of Olympic Records (Box 18)
  - Books- 1984 Guinness Book of Olympic Records (Box 18)
  - Books- 1988 Guinness Book of Olympic Records (Box 18)
  - Books- 1988 King Wally’s Olympic Fun Fact Book, Michael Walczewski (Box 18)
  - Books- 1992 Guinness Book of Olympic Records (Box 18)
  - Photo- Flame from Mt. Olympus, Greece (Box 19)
  - Photo- Panathenian Stadium-Athens (Box 19)
  - Publications- The Olympians- Evolution of the Games, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Publications- The Olympic Games from the U.S.O.C. Revised, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Publications- U.S.O.C. Fact Books, 1985, 1987, and 1989 (Box 19)
  - Publications- Olympic Review no60-62, no 125-126, no 239, no 252 (Box 19)
  - Publications- Olympic Message no, 18 August 1987 (Box 19)
  - Publications- The Olympian, June, July/August, September 1976 and March, July/August 1978 (Box 19)
  - Publications- The Olympian, December/January 1979/1980, May/June, July, August, October, November 1980 (Box 19)
  - Publications- The Olympian, March, Cover of June, October 1982, December/January 1982/1983, June, September, November/December 1983 (Box 19)
  - Publications- The Olympian, October/November, December 1984, May 1985, January 1987 (Box 19)
  - Publications- Sports Illustrated, July 19, 1976, August 2, 1976, and October 10, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Publications- Sports in the GDR, Montreal, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Publications- Stars in Motion Vol. 1 and Vol. 2, winter, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Publications- Track and Field News, August 1976 (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Correspondence (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Tracy Culkins (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Jack B. Kelly Jr. (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Olympic Clippings, also the Pan American Games (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Olympic Clippings and Materials (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Olympic Clippings (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Olympic Clippings (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Olympic Clippings (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Olympic Clippings (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Olympic Clippings (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Olympic Clippings (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Olympic Clippings (Box 19)
  - Misc.- Olympic Clippings (Box 19)
- Personal
  - Awards- APSE (Associated Press Sports Editors), Red Smith Award, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Awards- FWAA (Football Writers Association of America), McGrane Award, 1981 (Box 20)
  - Awards- Liberty Bowl, Distinguished Service Award, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Awards- Misc. (Box 20)
  - Awards- Misc. -mostly News Career (Box 20)
  - Awards- Nashville Banner, Celebrating 25 Years at the Nashville Banner (Box 20)
  - Awards- Nashville Banner, Celebrating 25 Years at the Nashville Banner (Box 20)
  - Awards- Nashville Banner, Celebrating 25 Years at the Nashville Banner (Box 20)
  - Awards- Nashville Banner, Celebrating 25 Years at the Nashville Banner (Box 20)
  - Awards- Nashville Banner, Celebrating 25 Years at the Nashville Banner (Box 20)
  - Awards- Nashville Banner, Emeritus status (Box 20)
  - Awards- NCAA (National Collegiate Athletic Association), A.A. Stagg Award, 1981 (Box 20)
  - Awards- NFFHF (National Football Federation and Hall of Fame), Distinguished American Award, 1980 (Box 20)
  - Awards- NFFHF (National Football Federation and Hall of Fame), Distinguished American Award, 1980 (Box 20)
  - Awards- Pulitzer Prize Nomination Materials (Box 20)
  - Awards- SME (Sales Marketing Executives), National Salesman of the Year, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Awards- SME (Sales Marketing Executives), National Salesman of the Year, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Awards- Sportsmenship Brotherhood, Grantland Rice Award, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Awards- Sportsmenship Brotherhood, Grantland Rice Award, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Awards- TRA (Thoroughbred Racing Association), Rice-Russell Scholarship at Vanderbilt University (Box 20)
  - Awards- Wartrace, Tennessee, Honoring Fred Russell at Homecoming, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence- Letters to be Answered (Box 20)
  - Correspondence- Misc. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence- Misc. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence- Misc. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence- Misc. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence- Misc. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence- Misc. (Some related to FR’s Promotion to VP) (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous- Clippings (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous- Clippings (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous- Hotel Reservations (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous- Humor Books (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous- Kappa Sigma (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous- Kappa Sigma (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous- Photos (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous- Photos (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous- Photos (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous- Retirement (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
- Personal and Miscellaneous (Large Flat Hollinger Box)
  - - Dossier Folder- Misc. (Box 21)
  - - Photo- 1906 Mooney Football Team (Box 21)
  - - Photo- Vanderbilt University Football Team, 1947 (Box 21)
  - - 1 lx 14 Black and White Photo Game in Progress (Box 21)
  - - Carrier’s Address to the Patrons of the Richmond Daily Dispatch Christmas 1850 - Mounted (Box 21)
  - - Newspapers from Fred Russell’s 25 Year Anniversary at the Banner Dinner (Box 21)
    - -Sept 3- Banner (Box 21)
    - -Sept 7- Banner (Box 21)
    - -Sept 8- Tennessee (Box 21)
    - -Sept 8- Banner (Box 21)
    - -Sept 9- Banner (Box 21)
    - -Sept 12- Banner (Box 21)
    - -Photos- Nashville Banner- Banquet of Champions 1960-1970’s (Box 21)
- Professional Career
  - AD Ideas (Box 22)
  - Chattanooga Daily Times and Chattanooga News-Free Press (Box 22)
  - Des Moines Sunday Register, June 19, 1949 (Box 22)
  - Gannett (Box 22)
  - Ideas - Book and story ideas (Box 22)
  - Improving Sports Section (Box 22)
  - Nashville Banner-Good Sports Pages (Box 22)
  - Nashville Banner- Sports School (Box 22)
  - The National Sports Daily- Premiere Issue, Jan 31, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Business (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Business (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Business (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Business (Box 22)
  - Newspaper- Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Newspaper- Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Newspaper- Miscellaneous (missing folder of originals) (Box 22)
  - Newspaper- Miscellaneous (missing folder of originals) (Box 22)
  - Newspaper- Miscellaneous (missing folder of originals) (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Operation (Box 22)
  - P.M. (Box 22)
  - Press Agentry (Box 22)
  - Public Relations (Box 22)
  - Saturday Evening Post (letters) (Box 22)
  - Sports Murals (Detroit News) (Box 22)
  - Sports Promotion- Ads (Box 22)
  - Wire Services (Box 22)
- General/Subject Files
  - Sports- Birthdays (Box 23)
  - Sports- Events (Top Sports Events of the Century) (Box 23)
  - Sports- Fascination and Value of Sports (Box 23)
  - Sports- Gambling and Fixing (Box 23)
  - Sports- Humor-Misc. Sports (Box 23)
  - Sports- Impact of Athletic Participation on Academic and Career Aspiration and Achievement, 1967 (Box 23)
  - Sports- Origin of Sports (Box 23)
  - Sports- Physical Education, Bud Wilkinson (Box 23)
  - Sports- Presidents in Sports (Box 23)
  - Sports- SEC Golden Anniversary (Box 23)
  - Sports- Sports Color, Perfection, Luck, and Unorthodoxy (Box 23)
  - Sports- Superstitions (Box 23)
  - Sports- Sports and War (Box 23)
  - Sports- The Why of Sports (Box 23)
  - Dates- New Years Greetings (Box 23)
  - Dates- Mother’s Day (Special Columns) (Box 23)
  - Dates- July 4th (Box 23)
  - Dates- Christmas, 1961-1965 (Box 23)
  - Dates- Poems- New Year’s Day, Washington’s Birthday, St. Patrick’s, July 4th, Thanksgiving, Christmas (Box 23)
  - Places- Atlanta (Box 23)
  - Places-Birmingham (Box 23)
  - Places-Califomia Trip, 1950 (Box 23)
  - Places-Califomia (Box 23)
  - Places-Canada, 1965 (Box 23)
  - Places-Cuba (Box 23)
  - Places-England (Box 23)
  - Places-Europe, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Places-Florida (Box 23)
  - Places-Green Bay Wisconsin (Box 23)
  - Places- Knoxville (Box 23)
  - Places-Las Vegas (Box 23)
  - Places-Los Angeles (Box 23)
  - Places-Mexico (Box 23)
  - Places-Nashville- What I like About Nashville (Box 24)
  - Places-New Orleans (Box 24)
  - Places-New York City (Box 24)
  - Places-New York, 1953 (Box 24)
  - Places-South (Box 24)
  - Places-Texas- Houston (Box 24)
  - Places-U.S. (Box 24)
  - Places-U.S. Cities (Birmingham, Charleston, Cincinnati, Memphis) (Box 24)
  - Places-Washington (Box 24)
  - General- Annoying Execs (Box 24)
  - General- Aspen Health Center (Box 24)
  - General- Benson, Maxwell (Box 24)
  - General- Carnegie Foundation Report, 1931 (Box 24)
  - General- Gags and Misprints (Box 24)
  - General- Gags and Misprints (Box 24)
  - General- Phil Harris (Box 24)
  - General- Herbert Hoover (Box 24)
  - General- Douglas MacArthur (Box 24)
  - General - Media, Local Program Ideas (Box 24)
  - General - Media, Newspaper/Radio (Box 24)
  - General - Media, Pigskin Preview, Proposed Radio Program (Box 24)
  - General - Media, Radio/Television (Box 24)
  - General - Media, TV and Sports (Box 24)
  - General- Memorial Resolutions (Box 24)
  - General- Nashville Business (Box 24)
  - General- Non-Sport (Box 24)
  - General- Odlund’s Island (Box 24)
  - General- Park Vista (Box 24)
  - General- Photos (Box 24)
  - General- Poems, Non-Sport (Box 24)
  - General- Poems, Jesse Wills (Box 24)
  - General- Quote (Box 24)
  - General- Race Relations (Box 24)
  - General- Sigma Delta Chi (Box 24)
  - General- Sigma Delta Chi- Omicron Delta Kappa (Box 24)
  - General- Stories and Songs (Box 24)
  - General- Tom Swifties (Box 24)
  - General- Turkey Hunt (Box 24)
  - General- World War II (Box 24)
  - General- Misc. found in the bottom of the filing cabinets (Box 24)
  - General- Misc, 1966 (Box 24)
  - General- Misc. (Box 24)
  - General- Unlabeled (Box 24)
  - General- Unlabeled (Box 24)
- Subject Files/Sports (Minor Sports in the collection)
  - Auto Racing (Box 25)
  - Basketball, 1952/1953/1954 (Box 25)
  - Basketball, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Basketball- VU (Box 25)
  - Basketball- Fix (Box 25)
  - Basketball- Celtics (Box 25)
  - Basketball- Globetrotters (Box 25)
  - Basketball- Kentucky Suspension (Box 25)
  - Basketball- UK Legacy (Box 25)
  - Basketball- Wonder Five Bill Fox (Box 25)
  - Bike Racing (Box 25)
  - Billiards (Box 25)
  - Bowls (Box 25)
  - Bowling (Box 25)
  - Boxing (Box 25)
  - Boxing- Boxer Sketches (Box 25)
  - Boxing- Famous Fights (Box 25)
  - Boxing- Heavyweight History (Box 25)
  - Boxing- Liston-Clay (Box 25)
  - Bull Fighting (Box 25)
  - Cock Fighting (Box 25)
  - Cricket (Box 25)
  - Dogs- Racing (Box 25)
  - Dogs- Show (Box 25)
  - Figure Skating (Box 25)
  - Fishing (Box 25)
  - Fox Hunting (Box 25)
  - Golf- Humor (Box 25)
  - Golf- Misc. (Box 26)
  - Golf- Misc. (Box 26)
  - Golf- Misc. (Box 26)
  - Golf- 1984 PGA Championship at Shoal Creek (Box 26)
  - Golf- 1990 PGA Championship at Shoal Creek (Box 26)
  - Golf- The Master at Augusta (Records and Stats 1934-1992) (Box 26)
  - Hunting (Box 26)
  - Ice Hockey (Box 26)
  - Jai-Lai (Box 26)
  - Poker (Box 26)
  - Polo (Box 26)
  - Rowing /Yachting (Box 26)
  - Rugby (Box 26)
  - Skiing (Box 26)
  - Soap Box Derby (Box 26)
  - Soccer (Box 26)
  - Swimming (Box 26)
  - Tennis, 1966 (Box 26)
  - Tennis- Davis Cup (Box 26)
  - Tennis- Misc. (Box 26)
  - Tennis- Pro Tennis (Box 26)
  - Tennis- Sketches (Box 26)
  - Track, 1960 (Box 26)
  - Track- Misc. (Box 26)
  - Track- Records (Box 26)
  - Track - SEC (Box 26)
  - Track- Negros in Track (Box 26)
  - Track- Pole Vaulting (Box 26)
  - Trap Shooting (Box 26)
  - Wrestling- The Business (Box 26)
  - Wrestling- Sketches (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous Sports (Box 26)
- VU Non-Sports
  - VU- Alumni- 1954 Alumni Association, Speaker at NYC VU Alumni Association Dinner (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1959 Alumni Association (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1959 Executive Committee (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1959-1960 Alumni Association (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1960 Alumni Association (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1960 Alumni Association (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1960 Alumni Association - James Lawson (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1960-1961 Alumni Association/ Board of Trust (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1960-1961 Executive Committee (Box 27)
  - VU-Alumni- 1961 Alumni Association (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1961 Alumni Association (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1961 Alumni Association (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1961 Alumni Association June 3rd Meeting (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1961 Alumni and Industry (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1961 Joint Committee (Alumni Association/ Board of Trust) (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1961 Joint Committee (Alumni Association/ Board of Trust) (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1961 Public Relations (Branscomb Meeting) (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1961 Public Relations (Box 27)
  - VU- Alumni- 1961-1962 Alumni Association (Box 27)
  - VU- Anniversary- Semi-sesquicentennial (Box 27)
  - VU- Application, 1996 (Box 27)
  - VU- Cooper, Norman (Box 27)
  - VU- Cousins, Norman, 1974 (Box 27)
  - VU- Fleming, Sam (Box 27)
  - VU- Heard, Alexander (Box 27)
  - VU- Lawrence, Admiral William (Box 27)
  - VU- Sarratt, Madison (Box 27)
  - VU- Thompson, Hall (Shoal Creek) (Box 27)
  - VU- Zerfoss, Thomas (Box 27)
  - VU- Quinq 1927 Class Reunion (Box 27)
  - VU- Quinq 1980 (Box 27)
  - VU- Speeches (Box 27)
  - VU- Speeches Alumni (Box 27)
  - VU- Non Sport (Box 27)
  - VU - 1967 Vanderbilt Entrance Requirements Committee Report (Box 27)
- VU Sports
  - VU- Memorial Gym (Box 28)
  - VU- World League of American Football, Proposed use of Stadium (Box 28)
  - VU- Mayor’s Stadium Study Committee Report, 1977 (Box 28)
  - VU- Dudley Field (Box 28)
  - VU- Stadium History (Box 28)
  - VU- Stadium (Box 28)
  - VU- Waston Brown, Gerry DiNardo, Paul Hoolahan (Box 28)
  - VU- Paul Hoolahan (Box 28)
  - VU- Fred Russell (Box 28)
  - VU- Clay Stapleton (Box 28)
  - VU- Hall Thompson/ Joe B. Wyatt (Box 28)
  - VU- 1992 SEC Opponents (Box 28)
  - VU- Athletics (Box 28)
  - VU- Curry Day-Curry Scholarship (Box 28)
  - VU- Morrison, Ray (Ray Morrison Day) (Box 28)
  - VU- Football Alumni (Box 28)
  - VU- 1922 Team (Box 28)
  - VU- 1935-1937 Team (Box 28)
  - VU- 1940 Games (Box 28)
  - VU- 1940 Athletics Publicity (Box 28)
  - VU- 1941 VU/Sewanee 50th Celebration (Box 28)
  - VU- 1942 Games (Box 28)
  - VU- 1942, 1943 Photos (Box 28)
  - VU- 1945 VU Football (Box 28)
  - VU- 1948 Games (Box 28)
  - VU- 1948 Vanderbilt/Yale (Box 28)
  - VU- 1971 Hustler Homecoming Supplement (Box 28)
  - VU- 1995, 1996 Football (Box 28)
  - VU- Vanderbilt/Vols Flashbacks (Box 28)
  - VU- Old Vanderbilt Games-Deeds-History (Box 28)
  - VU- Scrapbook (Box 28)
  - VU- Football Setup (Box 28)
  - VU- VU/Peabody Sports merger (Box 28)
- Writing
  - Style- Accuracy and Style (Box 29)
  - Style- American Press Institute (Box 29)
  - Style- Baseball Writing (Box 29)
  - Style- Clever Handling (Sports Stories) (Box 29)
  - Style- Cliches (Box 29)
  - Style- Columning (Box 29)
  - Style- Georgia Press Institute (Box 29)
  - Style- Humor (Future Book- Non-Sport) (Box 29)
  - Style- Magazine (Box 29)
  - Style- Sports Quotations (Box 29)
  - Style- Sportswriting (Box 29)
  - Style- UT Writing Seminar, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Style- UT Writing Seminar 1980 (Column Writing) (Box 29)
  - Style- Writing - Misc. (Box 29)
  - Style- Writing - Good Writing, 1957 (Box 29)
  - Style- Writing- Exceptionally Good Writing (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Atlanta Touchdown Club, 1947 (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Ensworth (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Fostoria, April 1951 (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Greenville Touchdown Club, 1958 (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Harpeth Hall (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Newspaper Speeches (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Quarterback Clubs (Box 29)
  - Speeches- St. Louis (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Strike Three (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Tallahassee Sept, 1952 (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Touchdown Club Speeches (Box 29)
  - Speeches- 1951, Speaking Notes (Box 29)
  - Speeches- 1952, Speaking Notes (Box 29)
  - Speeches, 1964, 1965 (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Speech Clips and Letters (Box 29)
  - Speeches- Undated (Box 29)
  - Speeches- (Box 29)
  - Speeches- (Box 29)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Athlon, 1982 (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Auburn (Saturday Evening Post) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Big Game (Packard Sports Library) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Basketball (Field Goals from Farm Boys in the Southern Agriculturalist (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Florida-Miami Clippings and Letters (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Gilmour (Colliers) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Guest Columns (Sideline Sidelights) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Huie (Colliers ) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Kentucky Basketball (1947 Sport Magazine) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Logue (Southern Living Magazine) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Minor League Managers Poll (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Miscellaneous Columns (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Miscellaneous Columns (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Grantland Rice (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Sidelines Sidelights, March 9, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Southern Football, Golden Age of Sports (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Southern Football, 1951 (Allsports) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Southern Football Recruiting (Saturday Evening Post) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Southern League (Allsports) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Southern Sports 1948-1949 (Allsports) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Bill Spivey Story (Sport) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Sport (Sportalk) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Sports Illustrated Rebuttal on Sportswriting (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Sports Week (Sports Illustrated) (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Louise Suggs (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Timeless Columns (Box 30)
  - Subject Files and Stories- Tittle (Box 30)
  - (Hollinger Box Letter)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Once There Was a Country Town (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, You Gotta Be Lucky (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, The Gold Rubs Off (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, The Toy Department (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Don’t Forget He’s a General (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Football Will Never Be the Same (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Names That Fit and Names That Don’t (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Is It Charging or Blocking? (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Spring Training (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Gooch-More of Baseball’s Peculiar Drollery (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Golf (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Racing (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Racing- Joe Palmer (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Racing- Keeneland (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Grantland Rice (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Grantland Rice- The Man Who Made Sportswriting (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, How to Write a Column (Box 31)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, How to Write a Column Every Damned Day (Box 31)
  - (Hollinger Box Legal)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Print Plate for Cover (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, For the Rest of My Life (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, The Pageantry of the People (Novel) (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Fun Lovers (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, More Fun Lovers (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Major League and Bush (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Basketball (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Miscellaneous (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Advertisement (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Notes (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Future Book (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Next Book (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Next Book, Continued (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Next Book, Continued (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Book, “Sportswriter” (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Card from Carolyn Russell to Fred Russell on the Publication (Box 32)
  - Manuscripts- Bury Me in an Old Press Box, Jacket and Publicity (Box 32)
  - One Paige box filled with Assorted files. A few are labeled, most are not. These Materials will need a finer sorting to be integrated in to the main portion of the collection.—Hosanna Banks (July 2000) (Box 33)
  - Two large flat Hollinger boxes have been added, they house several over sized items as well as all the materials that have been removed from frames. (Box 33)
  - There are 6 or 7 newly added Paige boxes that have not been had their preservation photocopies made and have not had their initial sort. (Box 33)